module.exports = 
{
  //0 a, 1 b, 2 c, 3 d,
  0:
      {
        prompt:"Why might removing food cues help with waist management? <br>A: Out of sight out of mind, <br>B: if we eat less then we create less waist, <br> C: The sight of food triggers the hippothalamus that makes it harder to manage waist<br>D: It is from our caveman times ",
        ans: 0
      },
      1:
      {
        prompt:"As hours of TV watched, skinfold fat measure_____<br>A: Decreases<br>B: Increases<br>C: Doesn't Changed<br>D: Kind of Decreases",
        ans: 1
      },
      2:
      {
        prompt:"Boys are more likely than girls to have a greater measure of skinfold fat?<br>A: True<br>B: False<br>C: I don't know<br>D: Among us",
        ans: 1
      },
      3:
      {
        prompt: "Why does exercising help with waist management?<br>A: It burns calories<br>B: It unclogs our rectum track and creates a smoother handling of waste<br>C: It empties fat cells, builds muscle, speeds up metabolism, and lowers set point<br>D: It makes our stomach acid be more efficent when handling food intake",
        ans: 2
      },
      4:
      {
        prompt: "Eating slow can lead to eating ____ <br>A: more<br>B: the same amount<br>C: I don't know<br>D: less",
        ans: 3
      },
      5:
      {
        //fix this
        prompt: "Name cultural factors that influences hunger:<br>A: culture, enviorment, and Neophobia<br>B: ethnicities and genetics from it<br>C: nothing<br>D: Differenting structure of admoninal track ",
        ans: 0
      },
      6:
      {
        prompt: "What is neophobia?<br>A: Neophobia is the liking of unfamillar things<br>B: Neophobia is the liking of famillar things<br>C: Neophobia is the dislike of unfamillar things<br>D: Neophobia is the dislike of famillar things",
        ans: 2
      },
      7:
      {
        prompt: "What category (cultural or situtational) does social faclitation fall in, and how does influence hunger?<br>A: cultural - Our heritage influences our hunger<br>B: situtational - We tend to eat less with more people around us<br>C: cultural - The people we live with influences our hunger<br>D: situational - We tend to eat more with more people around us",
        ans: 3
      },
      8:
      {
        //fix
        prompt: "What can influence our individual preferences?<br>A: age, genetics, and conditioning<br>B: race, genetics, and sex<br>C: we conciously decide what we will prefer<br>D: conditioning, culture, and situation",
        ans: 3
      },
      9:
      {
        prompt: "Of what does our hungry reflect our memory?<br>A: The rate at which we eat<br>B:  What we last ate and our expectation of when we should eat it<br>C: The taste and how beneficial it is to our body<br>D: The rate at which we eat and the taste of the food",
        ans: 1
      },
      10:
      {
        prompt: "Is hunger only from the stomach?<br>A: Yes<br>B: No<br>C: Maybe<br>D: @soljaxon on instagram",
        ans:1
      },
      11:
      {
        prompt: "Which is a factor in increased hunger?<br>A: Low glucose levels<br>B: High glucose levels<br>C: weight<br>D: none of the above",
        ans:0
      },
      12:
      {
        prompt: "Which is NOT an appetite hormone?<br>A: Insulin<br>B: Ghrelin<br>C: Dopamine<br>D: Leptin",
        ans:2
      },
      13:
      {
        prompt: "What is the Basal metabolic rate?<br>A: The speed at which we eat<br>B: Body's resting rate<br>C: The limit at which we can eat<br>D: Body's metabolism rate",
        ans:1
      },
      14:
      {
        prompt: "What is it called at the point which an individuals 'weight thermostat' is supposedly set?<br>A: Set point<br>B: hunger baseline<br> C: Basal metabolic rate<br>D: none of the above",
        ans:0
      },
      15:
      {
        prompt: "What are some good reasons why we store fat?<br>A: To keep us moisturized<br>B: To increase mass and power<br>C: To make us taller<br>D: Store energy and high calorie fuel",
        ans:3
      },
      16:
      {
        prompt: "What are some things obesity significantly increases?<br>A: risk of cramps<br>B: risk of diabetes and heart disease<br>C: risk of diabetes and tumours<br>D: risk of low appetite",
        ans:1
      },
      17:
      {
        prompt: "What is weight correlations twins have?<br>A: +.0 +.0<br>B: +.41 +.59<br>C: +.74 and +.34<br>D: 1.0 1.0",
        ans:2
      },
      18:
      {
        prompt: "What will most likely happen when you are socially influenced by an obese person?<br>A: You are more liekly to become overweight<br>B: You are less likely to become overweight<br>C: It has no influence<br>D: you will convience them become less overweight",
        ans:0
      }
}